United University Professions (UUP), Oral History Project; Records apap099
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
United University Professions (UUP) Oral History Project Collection
1968-2003
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap099
2.73 cubic ft. plus 66 audio tapes
The UUP Oral History Project's intent was to capture the history of the UUP as well as its predecessors through interviews with union executives and members.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted with the exception of several folders which are marked. While Dr. Ivan Steen, the Project's Director, subsequently asked individuals interviewed for the oral history projects he conducted to sign a clearance form or an agreement, not all interview files donated to the archive contain forms. In addition, some individuals asked for their interviews to be permanently sealed or sealed until a later date. Therefore notes, transcripts and audio of a select number of interviews are restricted until clearance may be obtained from the interviewees or their heirs.
Acquisition Information
The M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives received the UUP Oral History Project Collection in a series of donations, from Tom Curringham in 1994, Cindy Sauer in 1999, and Dr. Ivan Steen in 2000 and 2012-2013.
Organizational Sketch
United University Professions (UUP), established in 1973, is the collective bargaining agent representing the faculty and non-teaching professional staff of the State University of New York (SUNY). The United University Professions Oral History Project was funded by UUP and conducted by the Oral History Program of the Department of History, University at Albany, SUNY, under the supervision of Professor Ivan D. Steen. The primary intent of the UUP Oral History Project was to document the early history of UUP and its predecessor organizations. Angelica Lewis, a University at Albany graduate student in Public History, was hired to conduct the interviews. After researching UUP's history and conducting preliminary interviews with numerous people formerly and currently active in UUP, Lewis formally interviewed forty-two individuals. Those interviews were conducted between February and October 1990.
Topics of discussion include UUP's early history and its predecessor (the Senate Professional Association [SPA]) and other organizations that attempted to become the bargaining agent of the faculty and professional staff at SUNY, including the State University Federation of Teachers (SUFT, which would later merge with SPA to form UUP) and the American Association of University Professors (AAUP); the interviewees' reasons for becoming active in UUP; events and activities at various SUNY campuses regarding collective bargaining, UUP's predecessors, and UUP; negotiations and other dealings with the State of New York, and the individuals from the Governor's Office of Employee Relations who were involved in the negotiating process; the individual personalities that made up the early UUP leadership; internal political activities at UUP, particularly its Reform Caucus and United Caucus; the creation and impact of the agency fee law on UUP and its members; the challenge to UUP's position as collective bargaining agent in 1978 by the National Education Association and its affiliate, the New York Educators Association (NEA/NYEA); and the different objectives/interests of academic and professional members in the bargaining unit represented by UUP.
Scope and Contents
The United University Professions (UUP) Oral History Project Collection consists of four series: the recorded audio tapes of the formal oral history interviews, transcripts of those interviews, the interviewer's research files including her interview notes and materials she collected on UUP, and the project's administrative files.
The interviews primarily focus on the early history of UUP from the activities in the early 1970s of the Senate Professional Association (SPA) and the State University Federation of Teachers (SUFT) which merged to form UUP in 1973 through the administrations of UUP's first three presidents (Lawrence DeLucia, Samuel Wakshull, and Nuala McGann Drescher, who served between May 1973 to May 1987), and part of the administration of UUP's fourth president, John M. Reilly, who was president at the time the interviews were conducted in 1990.
Records regarding the activities of UUP during this time period, and relating to the many of the events, individuals, and organizations to which interviewees refer, can be found in the records of United University Professions (APAP-039). The records of the United University Professions (UUP) Albany Chapter (APAP-054) document some of the activities of this UUP chapter. Interested researchers also should condult the papers of Eugene Link (APAP-025), a professor of history at SUNY Plattsburgh who was active in the early years of UUP and in UUP's establishment of membership for retired members. Link's papers focus on his career as a teacher, author, social historian, labor activist, and Christian minister. The records of WAMC/Northeast Public Radio (APAP-138) include episodes of programs on which UUP leaders appeared.
For a detailed history of UUP itself, see the Administrative History for the records of United University Professions (APAP-039).
For more oral histories conducted by Dr. Ivan Steen, researchers should refer to the Ivan Steen Papers (APAP-219).
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series:
Series 1 - Audio Tapes, 1990
Series 2 - Interview Transcripts, 1990
Series 3 - Interview Notes and Background Material, 1968-1996, Undated
Series 4 - Administrative Files, 1989-2000, Undated
All series are arranged alphabetically.
State University of New York SUNY, Central Administration; Social Activists and Public Advocates; Labor; Education; Albany, New York; Oral history--New York (State); Labor union members--New York (State); Labor unions--New York (State); Audio cassettes; Interviews; Transcripts; Articles; Correspondence; Steen, Ivan D., 1936-; Drescher, Nuala McGann; Budin, Morris, 1920-; United University Professions (Association: N.Y.)
- Audio Tapes, 1990; 1; 66 Audio Tapes
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  Recorded tapes of oral history interviews. All interviews were transcribed and the transcripts are located in Series 2. The labels for a few of the tapes indicate that they were the first of two interviews; however, additional interviews were never conducted. Access to some tapes is either permanently or temporarily restricted, as noted in the box and folder list.
  - Alfonsin, Edward J. TAPES 1-4 AVAILABLE FOR RESEARCH, TAPE 5 SEALED PERMANENTLY, 1990 August 15 (Cassette 1-5)
    Conditions Governing Access
    As a condition ultimately granting release of his 1990 interview, Edward Alfonsin asked for the full interview to be released in 2023 but to remove one setence and one phrase appearing on tape 5 which is part of Series 1. The interview transcript, minus these two parts, was released in 2023 in accordance with his wishes. Researchers may listen to tapes 1-4 in Series 1 and read both the typed transcript (Series 2) and the corrected version (Series 4). Tape 5, which contains the two small parts that Alfonsin would not agree to release, is permanently sealed and not available to researchers for listening.
  - Atkins, Bruce, 1990 March 23 (Cassette 6)
  - Budin, Morris, 1990 October 12 (Cassette 7-8)
  - Burelbach, Fred TAPE 9 SEALED PERMANENTLY, TAPE 10 AVAILABLE FOR RESEARCH, 1990 May 15 (Cassette 9-10)
    As a condition ultimately granting release of his 1990 interview, Fred Burelbach asked for three pages to be removed. The interview transcript, minus these three pages, was released in accordance with his wishes. Reesearchers may read both the typed transcript (Series 2) and the corrected version (Series 4) and listen to tape 2 (Series 1). The three corrected pages and tape 1 of the interview are permanently sealed.
  - Cimineli-Geerken, Diane, 1990 May 04 (Cassette 11)
  - Cozort, William, 1990 May 04 (Cassette 12)
  - Crary, John, 1990 October 13 (Cassette 13-14)
    Sealed permanently.
  - Davidson, Robert, 1990 May 04 (Cassette 15)
  - Drescher, Nuala, 1990 September 13 (Cassette 16-17)
  - Drew, Joseph, 1990 June 04 (Cassette 18-19)
  - Dubois, Robert, 1990 June 04 (Cassette 20-21)
  - Ether, Jack, 1990 August 17 (Cassette 22)
  - Geerken, Henry, 1990 May 04 (Cassette 23-24)
  - Granger, Robert [RESTRICTED], 1990 October 17-1990 October 18 (Cassette 25-28)
    Must consult archivist before viewing this material. This is restricted because Robert Granger never signed the release form for the UUP Oral History Project nor did he receive Professor Ivan Steen's 1995 certified letter, five years following the project, indicating that if the interviewee did not return the release form, provide a corrected copy of their transcript or provide other written instructions concerning their transcript, then the transcript would be considered approved and placed in the archives and available to researchers.
  - Gutenkauf, Dorothy, 1990 July 20 (Cassette 29-30)
  - Hall, Robert, 1990 April 05 (Cassette 31)
  - Hansen, Charles, 1990 February 19 (Cassette 32)
  - Hartman-Wakshull, Evelyn, 1990 April 19 (Cassette 33)
  - Inventasch, Harvey, 1990 March 01 (Cassette 34)
  - Knudsen, Doris, 1990 May 25 (Cassette 35-36)
  - Lamendola, Joseph, 1990 October 13 (Cassette 37)
  - Lauter, Paul TAPE 39 SEALED PERMANENTLY, TAPES 38 AND 40 AVAILABLE FOR RESEARCH, 1990 August 13 (Cassette 38-40)
    As a condition granting release of his 1990 interview, Paul Lauter asked for one page to be removed. The interview transcript, minus this page, was released in accordance with his wishes. Reesearchers may read both the typed transcript (Series 2) and the corrected version (Series 4) and listen to tapes 38 and 40 (Series 1). The one corrected page and tape 39 are permanently sealed.
  - Link, Eugene, 1990 April 06 (Cassette 41-42)
  - Maraviglia, Frank, 1990 August 10 (Cassette 43-44)
  - Matthews, Thomas, 1990 May 03 (Cassette 45)
  - McCaffery, Lyle, 1990 October 12 (Cassette 46-47)
  - Nelson, Malcolm A, 1990 March 23 (Cassette 48)
  - Piccolo, Rita, 1990 June 05 (Cassette 49-50)
  - Potter, Janet, 1990 August 20 (Cassette 51)
  - Potter, Robert, 1990 March 15 (Cassette 52)
  - Puretz, Susan L., 1990 March 23 (Cassette 53)
  - Ray, Frank, 1990 May 03 (Cassette 54-55)
  - Sanbonmatsu, Akira, 1990 October 12 (Cassette 56-57)
  - Santelli, Charles SEALED PERMANENTLY, 1990 April 04 (Cassette 58)
  - Schaffer, D. Jo, 1990 April 10 (Cassette 59)
  - Shank, Alan, 1990 March 02 (Cassette 60)
  - Steck, Henry SEALED PERMANENTLY, 1990 March 02 (Cassette 61)
  - Stewart, James, 1990 February 26 (Cassette 62)
  - Tiger, Elizabeth R., 1990 March 22 (Cassette 63)
  - Wakshull, Sam, 1990 April 19 (Cassette 64)
  - Wise, Josephine, 1990 March 22 (Cassette 65)
  - Yeracaris, Constantine, 1990 June 05 (Cassette 66-67)
- Interview Transcripts, 1990; 2; 0.95 cubic ft.
  Transcriptions of recorded interviews in Series 1. The interviews cover events and personalities from the years prior to UUP's creation in 1973 through the first years of the administration of its fourth president, John M. Reilly, who was president when the interviews were conducted in 1990. Interviewees include individuals who served as president of UUP, as members of UUP's Executive Board, as officers of UUP, or who were otherwise active in UUP's creation and early history. Some individual names are spelled irregularly from transcript to transcript. Consult the records of United University Professions, particularly publications such as The Voice for the correct spelling of individual names. The researcher should note that not all individuals in this series participated in a formal interview.
  - Alfonsin, Edward J., 1990 August 15 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 1-2)
  - Atkins, Bruce, 1990 March 23 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 3)
  - Budin, Morris, 1990 October 12 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 4)
  - Burelbach, Fred, 1990 May 15 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 5)
  - Cimineli-Geerken, Diane, 1990 May 04 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 6)
  - Cozort, William, 1990 May 04 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 7)
  - Crary, John, 1990 October 13 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 8)
  - Davidson, Robert, 1990 May 04 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 9)
  - Drescher, Nuala, 1990 September 13 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 10)
  - Drew, Joseph, 1990 June 04 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 11)
  - Dubois, Robert, 1990 June 04 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 12)
  - Ether, Jack, 1990 August 17 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 13)
  - Geerken, Henry, 1990 May 04 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 14)
  - Gutenkauf, Dorothy, 1990 July 20 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 15)
  - Hall, Robert, 1990 April 05 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 16)
  - Hansen, Charles, 1990 February 19 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 17)
  - Hartmann-Wakshull, Evelyn, 1990 April 19 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 18)
  - Inventasch, Harvey, 1990 March 01 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 19)
  - Knudsen, Doris, 1990 May 04 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 20)
  - Lamendola, Joseph, 1990 October 13 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 21)
  - Lauter, Paul, 1990 August 13 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 22)
  - Link, Eugene, 1990 April 06 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 23)
  - Maraviglia, Frank, 1990 August 10 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 24)
  - Matthews, Thomas, 1990 May 04 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 25)
  - Nelson, Malcolm A., 1990 March 23 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 26)
  - Potter, Janet, 1990 August 20 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 27)
  - Potter, Robert, 1990 March 15 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 28)
  - Puretz, Susan L., 1990 March 23 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 29)
  - Ray, Frank, 1990 May 03 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 30)
  - Sanbonmatsu, Akira, 1990 October 12 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 31)
  - Santelli, Charles SEALED PERMANENTLY, 1990 April 04 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 32)
  - Schaffer, D. Jo, 1990 April 10 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 33)
  - Shank, Alan, 1990 March 02 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 34)
  - Steck, Henry SEALED PERMANENTLY, 1990 March 02 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 35)
  - Stewart, James, 1990 February 26 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 36)
  - Tiger, Elizabeth, 1990 March 22 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 37)
  - Yeracaris, Constantine, 1990 June 05 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 38)
  - Wakshull, Sam, 1990 April 19 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 39)
  - Wise, Josephine, 1990 March 22 (Box 1 (2-Interview Transcripts), Folder 40)
- Interview Notes and Background Material, 1968-1996; Undated; 3; 0.55 cubic ft.
  The bulk of this series is made up of the interviewer's notes regarding each individual formally interviewed and potential interviewees. In addition to including the interviewer's handwritten notes taken during the formal taped interviews and during preliminary interviews with subjects, most interviewee files include a "UUP Potential Interview Candidate Fact Sheet", listing each individual's involvement in UUP at the statewide and chapter level (and in UUP's predecessors if applicable), including offices held and committees assigned to. Files for individuals formally interviewed often include an outline of issues to be covered during the interview and additional summaries of the individual's UUP activities.
  - Alfonsin, Edward J., 1990; Undated (Box 1 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 41)
  - Allen, John, Undated (Box 1 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 42)
  - Atkins, Bruce, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 43)
  - Brown, Neil, Undated (Box 1 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 44)
  - Budin, Morris, 1990; Undated (Box 1 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 45)
  - Burelbach, Fred (1 of 2), 1990; Undated (Box 1 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 46)
  - Burelbach, Fred (2 of 2), 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 1)
  - Cimineli-Geerken, Diane, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 2)
  - Corigliano, Thomas, Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 3)
  - Cozort, William, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 4)
  - Crary, John, ca. 1990 (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 5)
  - Cretekos, James, 1990 (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 6)
  - Davidson, Robert, 1990 (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 7)
  - Doh, Herman, 1989; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 8)
  - Drescher, Nuala, 1989; 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 9)
  - Drew, Joseph, 1989; 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 10)
  - Dubois, Robert, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 11)
  - Edwards, Mary, Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 12)
  - Encinio, Philip, 1990 (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 13)
  - Ermanovics, Albert, Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 14)
  - Ether, Jack, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 15)
  - Fasting, Joseph, Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 16)
  - "Ficcio, T" included with interviewee materials, but contains materials from UUP files regarding SUFT/SPA merger, AAUP, NEA and NYSUT, 1970-1975 (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 17)
  - Fleming, R. Thomas, Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 18)
  - Fox, Ernest, Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 19)
  - Geerken, Henry, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 20)
  - General Research, 1968-1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 21-22)
  - Gill, James, Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 23)
  - Glasheen, Richard, Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 24)
  - Granger, Robert, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 25)
  - Gutenkauf, Dorothy, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 26)
  - Hall, Robert, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 27)
  - Hansen, Charles, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 28)
  - Hartmann-Wakshull, Evelyn, 1990; 1995; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 29)
  - Hehn, Paul, Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 30)
  - Hotelling, Gail, Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 31)
  - Hunt, John, Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 32)
  - Interviewees-Special Cases (Buchalter, Patricia; Willsey, Alan; Hicks, Cheryl), Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 33)
  - Interview Short Lists, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 34)
  - Inventasch, Harvey, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 35)
  - Knudsen, Doris, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 36)
  - Kreh, David, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 37)
  - Lambert, Fred, Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 38)
  - Lamendola, Joseph, 1990 (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 39)
  - Lauter, Paul, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 40)
  - Link, Eugene, 1990; 1992; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 41)
  - Maraviglia, Frank, 1990 (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 42)
  - Mark, Francis X, Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 43)
  - Marsh, Leland, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 44)
  - Matthews, Thomas, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 45)
  - McCaffrey, Barbara, Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 46)
  - McCaffrey, Lyle, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 47)
  - Miller, Fred, Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 48)
  - Mitchell, George, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 49)
  - Nagler, Sylvain, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 50)
  - Nelson, Malcolm A., 1989-1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 51)
  - "Notes on Transcripts During Editing", Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 52)
  - Papers on Unions and Higher Education, 1986; 1987 (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 53)
  - Piccolo, Rita, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 54)
  - Potter, Janet, 1990 (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 55)
  - Potter, Robert, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 56)
  - Puretz, Susan L., 1990-1991; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 57)
  - Quattlebaum, Nathaniel, 1989; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 58)
  - Ray, Frank, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 59)
  - Reform Caucus Research, 1985; 1986; 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 60)
  - Reilly, John M. (Tim), 1989; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 61)
  - Reines/Raynes, Phillip, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 62)
  - Research Materials from John Valter, 1970; 1977; 1980; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 63)
  - Research on NYSUT Disaffiliation with NEA, from Drew's Files, 1975 (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 64)
  - Research on Committees, 1974-1990 (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 65)
  - Sanbonmatsu, Akira, Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 66)
  - Santelli, Charles, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 67)
  - Schaffer, D. Jo, Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 68)
  - Shank, Alan, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 69)
  - Smith, Bruce, Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 70)
  - Smith, Walter, Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 71)
  - Steck, Henry, 1989-1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 72)
  - Stewart, James, 1990 (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 73)
  - Teevan, Richard, 1989; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 74)
  - Tiger, Elizabeth, 1990; Undated (Box 2 (3-Interview Notes and Background Material), Folder 75)